{"showBridgeTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40185/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40185,"taskName":"Range \u0026 Hood - Clean","taskDescription":"Clean Range and Hood","xmTaskDescriptor":"Kitchen Exhaust \u0026 Hood Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":156,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Hood exhaust hoods cleaning maid","textMessagingName":"Cln Range Hood","rolloverLongDesc":"Primarily a commercial service, appropriate to larger scale or heavy-use home kitchens.","rolloverShortDesc":"Clean out accumulated grease from range \u0026 hood.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean Range and Hood.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Kitchen Exhaust \u0026 Hood Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Clean Range Hoods, Stoves, Ovens","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Range \u0026 Hood","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Range \u0026 Hood - Clean","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Range \u0026 Hood Cleaning Project","urlName":"Range-Hood-Clean","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Kitchen \u0026 Hood Cleaning Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Hood, exhaust, maid, clean, island, Range, grease, trap, kitchen, vent, restaurant, stove, rangehood","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":493,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"taskHeader":"Kitchen Exhaust \u0026 Hood Cleaning Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40185/":{"taskOID":40185,"originalTaskOID":40185,"setID":493,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4773,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What do you need cleaned? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3075,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hoods","answerDisplayText":"Hoods","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2852,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grease traps and drains","answerDisplayText":"Grease traps and drains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3419,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen equipment","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":767,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning Type Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of cleaning is needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7220,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Recurring Service","answerDisplayText":"Recurring Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4386,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One time cleaning","answerDisplayText":"One time cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4773,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What do you need cleaned? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3075,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hoods","answerDisplayText":"Hoods","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2852,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grease traps and drains","answerDisplayText":"Grease traps and drains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3419,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen equipment","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3075,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Hoods","answerDisplayText":"Hoods","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2852,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grease traps and drains","answerDisplayText":"Grease traps and drains","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3419,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Kitchen equipment","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen equipment","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":767,"questionDisplayText":"Cleaning Type Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of cleaning is needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7220,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Recurring Service","answerDisplayText":"Recurring Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4386,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One time cleaning","answerDisplayText":"One time cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7220,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Recurring Service","answerDisplayText":"Recurring Service","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4386,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"One time cleaning","answerDisplayText":"One time cleaning","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}